ourlost.com 2016-05-17

# Privacy Policy | Who Died Today | Our Lost

#### BY USING OR ACCESSING THIS WEBSITE, YOU ACCEPT AND AGREE TO ALL APPLICABLE LAWS AND REGULATIONS REGARDLESS OF LOCATION

The term “User”, shall refer to any individual or company representative who is representing an entity and its affiliates.  Any User that represents a company represents them as having the authority as an entity, and is stating they have full consent and authority from that company to bind all Terms of this Privacy Policy (“Terms”).

Users’ accept these Terms by simply accessing the ‘OurLost.com (“OurLost.com”, “we”; “our”; “us”) Website located at www.OurLost.com (“Website” or “Site”), which is owned and operated out of Ontario, Canada.  Terms are accepted not only when accessing the Website, but also when clicking any boxes indicating the Users’ acceptance or by completing any order forms that reference this Agreement or its Terms, and the User is agreeing to the Terms defined within this Agreement.  If for any reason a User does not agree with any Terms of this Agreement, the User is required to log off the Website immediately.

OurLost.com.me has developed this Privacy Policy for the User to understand how we collect, use, communicate and make use of any Users’ personal information.  When a User accesses our Website, we learn certain information during their visit.  Privacy is very important to us and so we take this Policy and its Terms seriously.  A User utilizing OurLost.com.me needs to read and follow all posted Agreements, Disclaimers and Policies pertaining to its usage regardless of physical location.

#### COOKIES

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier.  When a User visits OurLost.com, the computer asks each Users computer for permission to store a file in their hard-drive, specifically designated for cookies.  In addition, the Services can send its own cookie to a Users browser if the User sets their browser preferences to allow it, except if to protect User privacy the browser only permits access to the cookies it has already sent to the User.

Similar to other web services, OurLost.com utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” and “server logs” to collect information about how OurLost.com Services is used.  Information gathered through cookies and server logs may include the date and time of visits, pages viewed, time spent logged in, and the website/webpage/application visited just before and just after a User visits OurLost.com, including Users’ IP address.  OurLost.com Services shall collect information such as ‘clicks’ on any specific buttons deemed necessary by OurLost.com Services and shall collect information in connection with any ‘likes’ on any specific buttons deemed necessary within OurLost.com Services.

#### IP ADDRESSES 

IP addresses are used by a Users computer each time the User connects to the internet.  A Users IP address is a number used by computers on the network to identify the computer.  IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data and any page a User requests can be sent to the User.

#### EMAIL INFORMATION

If Users’ choose to correspond through email with OurLost.com or its webmaster using the specified “Contact” tab or any other wording we choice to use.  We may retain the content of the messages together with all responses.  We provide the same protection for these electronic communications that are employed in the maintenance of information received online, by mail or by telephone.

#### USER INFORMATION USAGE

Generally speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other items and Services to a User and prospective User.

OurLost.com will not obtain personally-identifying data about a User while visiting OurLost.com unless such User provides that information to us and it will never be sold or transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the User, at time of collection.  We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.

#### USER DATA PROTECTION

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication.  For this reason, we request Users’ do not send private information to us by email.  Conversely, doing so is allowed, but at Users own risk. OurLost.com may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as:

  * ssessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site;
  * What information is of most and least interest;
  * Determining technical design specifications;
  * dentifying system performance or problem areas;
  * Any other reason deemed necessary.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this Service remains available to Users, OurLost.com uses a software programs to monitor network traffic which identifies unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

#### POLICY CHANGES

OurLost.com reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time with or without notice.  Be assured if this Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information a User submitted to us under a previous Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without Users prior consent.  OurLost.com is committed to conducting business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.  If you have any questions regarding this Policy, or use of our Services, contact OurLost.com.
